# KIREE BELLAMY

## Junior Fullstack Developer

kireebellamy@gmail.com

+46 (0)73 417 2218

Stockholm

in www.linkedin.com/in/kireebellamy

https://github.com/Swewi

https://tinyurl.com/KireesCV

## About Me

I am a Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Fullstack Software Development from Code Institute. Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, and Django, but with much to learn!

I have 10+ years of experience in Customer Service and hospitality. I am a valuable team player with strong communication and problem-solving skills. I am keen to start working in the tech industry as a member of a development team where I can grow and contribute!

#### **KEY SKILLS**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python

Databases: MySQL, and postgres

Frameworks: Flask, Django, and Bootstrap Version Control: Heroku, GitHub, and Git

## COLLABORATION PROJECTS

 Code Institute Hackathon July 2024 - Proud Coders:

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication
- Compassion
- Creative Problem-solving
- Curiosity
- Persistence
- Resilience

#### PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

- Portfolio Project 5: Mildew detection in <u>cherry leaves</u> - A small streamlit and machine learning project to visualise powdery mildew on cherry leaves. I used Python and Streamlit for this project.
- Portfolio Project 4: Werecat Blog A blog site for a pair of crafty women. I used HTML, CSS vanilla and Bootstrap, JavaScript, Python, Postgres, and Django for this project.
- Portfolio Project 3: Wings Text-Based Game - A good old-fashioned 'pick a path' textbased game. I used Python for this project.
- Portfolio Project 2: Testing your STP knowledge - A short quiz game to test your Terry Pratchett knowledge. I used JavaScript, HTML, and CSS for this project.
- Portfolio Project 1: NZ Wars a brief overview - A very brief overview of the New Zealand Wars. I used HTML, and CSS for this project.

# KIREE BELLAMY

# Junior Fullstack Developer

+46 (0)73 417 2218

Stockholm

kireebellamy@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/kireebellamy



https://github.com/Swewi



https://tinyurl.com/KireesCV

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Business Startup - Sweet As!** Stockholm - Sweden 2021 - 2022

- · Writing and adapting business plans, to meet the changing economic environment.
- Writing and adapting budgets to meet the changing economic environment.
- Voluntarily suspending the start-up process due to massive upheaval in the economic climate.

## Skafferiet I Ekoparken Stockholm - Sweden 2017 - 2020

- Interact with customers and colleagues from around the world.
- Inform customers about available products, and any specials, take and deliver orders.
- Ability to switch between front and back of house multiple times per shift as required.

## Mountain Warehouse Portsmouth - Great Britain 2013 - 2015

- Maximising sales by using my personal experience of the brand and products.
- Building relationships with customers and colleagues to benefit customer experience.

### **EDUCATION**

#### **Code Institute**

Diploma in Fullstack Development Februrary 2024 - July 2024

#### **University of Auckland**

Bachelor of Science 1994 - 1999

### LANGUAGE

- English Native
- Swedish Basic

#### SHORT COURSES AND CERTIFICATES

• Le Wagon - Intro to SQL

#### **MEMBERSHIPS**

Tjejer Kodar

## Additional Information and Interests

- · I make and try to sell handcrafts, I work with paracord and rope making leashes, collars, braclets, keyrings, and weird bits and pieces. I make chainmaile bradelets and earings, and I use yarn, both natural and man-made, to nålbind. I am working on designing a website for my partner and I to use as a showcase and sales platform.
- I am designing a website my partner can use to track and see trends in their blood sugar levels.
- I enjoy gaming, I play minecraft primarily, however I do not limit myself to only PC gaming, I love playing on our switch, or the one of several consoles we have in the house.